Sewing Room
（邦枝）≪じゃあ　さっさと着替えてすませちゃいましょう≫
Okay, let's get changed
and get this over with.
（寧々）まったく　アイツらといると気が休まりませんよ。→
Man, I just can't let my
guard down with them around.
ねえ　姐さん。
（邦枝）そうねえ。
You know, Madam Aoi?
True, true...
（男鹿）最悪だ。何だ　この状況。
This sucks.
How'd we end up like this?
（古市）男鹿…。
（男鹿）え？
Oga...
（古市）断言するぞ。オレは
今のために→
This I swear...
I feel like my entire life
has led up to this moment...
生きてきた気がする。今　この場で
命が尽きたって構わない。
If my life ends here, so be it!
こんな体勢で
なに言ってんだ　テメーは。
What the hell are you saying
stuck under a desk?!
≪ってか　テメーのせいだろうが
何とかしろや！≫
This is all your damn fault! Do something!
（古市）≪母さん　生んでくれて
ありがとう≫
Mother, thank you for giving birth to me!
≪おい！聞いてんのか
テメー≫
Hey! Are you even listening to me?
（古市）＜古市です。オレ達が
何で　こんな事に→
Furuichi here.
What exactly led up to
this situation, you ask?
なったかというと　話は
１時間ほど前に　さかのぼります＞
It all started about one hour ago...
（ベル坊）…キ。キー。
（邦枝）身体測定ですか？
Physicals?
（佐渡原）そうだ。午後の授業の
代わりにな。
Yes. Instead of class this afternoon.
それで　私達に何を？
And what does that have to do with us?
（佐渡原）計測は普通　担当の
保健委員が→
Usually the measurements are taken by the
assigned student health representative,
やるもんだが
マジメな学生の時間を→
but we can't waste the time of one of our
serious students on you future dropouts.
お前らのような
おちこぼれに使う訳にはいかん。
（佐渡原）オレも　いろいろ忙しい
クラス委員の→
I'm busy with a lot of things myself.
You two class reps handle your
class's measurements yourselves.
お前が達が仕切って
自分達でやれ。
場所は職員室の隣の。
あ～！
You'll do it in the room next
to the teachers' office...
ん？
引っ張んな　ベル坊！
Stop pulling on that, Baby Beel!
って聞いてんのか！
あ？あ～聞いてる　聞いてる。
Are you listening to me?!
Oh, sure I am...
《く…こいつは》
This guy...
((悲鳴))
《なめた態度とりやがって…
まあいい。→
He thinks I'm a pushover!
Whatever...
あいつらが身体測定なんぞ
マジメにやるはずがない。→
There's no way they'll be
able to do a proper physical.
少しでも暴れれば
こっちのものだ。→
Run a little bit amok,
and your asses are mine.
すぐに退学に追い込んでやる》
A one-way ticket to expulsion!
Let's All Get Physicals!
（ぐずる声）
おい　いい加減に…。
Give it a rest!
（寧々）
姐さん　呼び出し何でしたか？
Madam Aoi, what did you call us out here for?
（邦枝）身体測定をやれって。
We've been told to do physical exams.
（千秋・寧々・由加）は？
（由加）身体測定っすか？
Physicals?
ええ。おまけに
クラス委員で仕切って→
Yeah... And we class reps were told
to do everyone's physicals ourselves.
自分達で計れって
言われたんだけど。
（ぐずる声）
これじゃね。何か　いつもより
ぐずってない？
But...
Isn't he squirming a little more than usual?
退屈してんだよ。こいつ
転校して来てから→
He's bored!
Since we transferred, we haven't
been allowed to make trouble.
学校じゃ　もめ事　禁止だからな。
He's agitated and pisses himself all day.
四六時中わめくわ　おもらしするわ
引っ張んなっつ～の。
ビビビ…ダ～！
I said not to pull that!
（ぐずる声）
やりたかないですけど　私らも
手伝った方が良くないですか？→
I'd rather not... But wouldn't
it be better if we helped?
男の計測。
（ぐずる声）
The guy's measurements...
そうね　先に行って準備してて。
私は→
Yeah.
Go on ahead and get ready.
I'll go call the rest of the class.
他の連中を呼んで来るから。
あ　１つ注意点
とにかく騒ぎを起こさない事。→
One warning:
Whatever you do, don't make a scene.
佐渡原のヤツ　少しでも騒いだら
問題にしてやるって→
Sadohara's acting like he'll make
a big deal out of any trouble.
雰囲気だったから。
ハ！
（下川）グッナイ　子猫ちゃん。
オレと→
Good night, little kitty.
How'd you like to have a
nice dream together with me?
一緒に良い夢　見てみないかい？
（梓）えっと～。言ってる意味が
分かんないんですけど。
Um...
I don't know what you're saying actually.
っていうか　何で中途半端に
英語使ってるんですか？
And why do you use such half-assed English?
こ　このバカどもが～！
Y-You...
...total idiots!
≪ちょっと　それどけて≫
≪よいしょ≫
Move that over there...
Sewing Room
アイダブ！
オブ！ダブダブダブ
アイアイアイ。
ダブアイ　ダブアイ。
ダブダブアイ！
いいぞ　ベル坊。攻めろ　攻めろ！
That's the way, Baby Beel! Close in!
Watch out for his punches!
パンチに気を付けろよ。あ～！
あ…。
ベル坊！体を起こせ。
体を起こせ　ベル坊～！
Baby Beel!
Straighten up!
Straighten up, Baby Beel!
立てで　いいだろ。
足を使ってイイ感じに　ほら。
っと　な！
You mean stand up, right?
Use your legs, get set,
and then, all at once...
だから　立てで　いいだろ！
わざとか？
Just tell him to, "stand up"!
Are you doing this on purpose?
え？
何だテメー　その顔
やんのか　コラ！
What're you givin' me that look for?
You wanna go, buddy?
ダブダ！ダブダ　ダブダ。アイ！
マ！ダ　ブ　ダ。
フ…見事に　東条と戦ったオレを→
He did a pretty sweet re-enacting of
my fight with Tojo, don't you think?
再現してるじゃねえか。
（古市）あ～じゃあ。→
So then, that's Lamia...
あれがラミアで
上がフォルカスで→
Above is Furcas...
横がヒルダさん
アランドロン…で何？→
Beside him is Hilda-san...
Alaindelon, and then, what?
あれがオレな訳？何なの！
あの憎たらしい顔→
Is that thing supposed to be me?
What's with that horrible face?
何で車に乗ってんの！
Why's it riding a car?
（由加）
ぱねえっすね！寧々さん　何で
こんなに→
Like, totally hardcore!
Why're there so many stuffed
animals here, Nene-san?
ぬいぐるみ置いてあるんすかね。
あ～何か手芸部が　普段→
Yeah...
Looks like this room is usually
used for the arts and crafts club.
部室として使ってるらしいわよ。
千秋　そっち持って。
Chiaki, carry that.
（千秋）うん。
ふぁ～。
Right.
なあ男鹿。オレは今　幸せだぞ。
あ？
Oga... I'm so happy right now.
女子が男子の身体測定をやる。
これだよ！
The girls are gonna do the boys' physicals.
This is what I'm talking about!
こういう普通のイベントが
足りなさ過ぎたんだよ　今までは。
I've been missing these
kinds of school-year events!
There've been so few!
ちょっと男子。見てないで
手伝いな！
Hey, boys! Stop gawking and start helping.
そ～だよ男鹿っち。元々は
男鹿っちの仕事なんだから。
Yeah, Oga-chi!
This is your job in the first place!
うす！手伝います。
その前に…。
な　なによ。
Sure!
I'll help!
But before that...
W-What's...
今の　ちょっと男子っていうのを
声を高くして→
Could you take that,
"Hey, boys!" from before,
raise your pitch a little,
and go, "Hey, boys~" for me?
ちょっと男子～っていう風に
言い直して。
（邦枝）≪うりゃ　男子コラ～！≫
Hey, you dickheads!
どいつもこいつも！
ね　姐さん？
Each and every one of you!
M-Madam Aoi...
とっととやるわよ！準備して。
（３人）は　はい。
We're getting this over with!
Get ready.
Right.
（姫川）《…容赦ねえな
クイーン》
Queen, no mercy as always.
ったく　めんどくせえな。
Man, what a pain.
ショー。
ちょ　ちょっと何してんの。
W-What are you doing?
あ？身体測定っつったら
着替えんだろうが。
If we're doing physicals, we gotta
change out of our clothes, yeah?
き　着替えなら
隅の方でやんなさいよ。
If you're gonna change,
go do it in the corner!
あ？
ダ～ブ。
よっと。
ザックリ１８０センチ。
About 1.8 meters.
ぐ　グッナイ…。
G-Good night...
どうだ古市　うれしいか？
How about it, Furuichi?
This making you happy?
ちょっと　望んでたのとは…違う。
It's not quite what I'd hoped for.
あ～いいんすか？そのままで。
You sure it's okay like this?
い～っつってんだろ
サクッとやれ。
じゃあ…。
I said it's fine.
Hurry up and do it.
Okay...
えっと…ひゃ　ひゃく。
Uh... One meter and...
ひゃ　ひゃく。ハハハ…。
O-One meter and...
（笑い）
テメ～　コラ！
You jerks!
ちょっと騒がないで。隣
職員室なのよ。
Hey, keep it down.
The teachers' office is next door, you know.
あ？すっこんでろ…。
Hey, back off!
（神崎）へ～。
（夏目）へえ。
（城山）ほう。
な　何？
What?
え？
意外と　あれだな。着やせする…。
I guess you're one of those where
the clothes make you lose a few...
（暴れる音）
《ん？何だ今の音は。まあいい
問題を起こせば　その時は…》
What was that noise?
Whatever...
If they cause any problems, then...
はい　おしまい！そこの２人も
着替えたら出てってよ。
Okay, finished!
When you two are done changing, get out!
次　女子だから。
（古市）ええ？もう終わりっすか。
The girls are next.
It's over already?
ウチら　着替え取って来るんで。
じゃ　じゃあ→
We're going to get changed.
So since the girls helped the guys,
that means the guys'll help the...
女子が男子のを
手伝ったんですから→
男子が女子のを…。
Shut up!
ん？
ギャ。ギャ～！
バーブー。
大丈夫か　お前。
You okay there?
とっとと出て行け　この変態！
Get out of here, freak!
（ドアの閉まる音）
おい　ベル坊　行くぞ！ん？
Come on, Baby Beel. Let's go.
（ロッカーの閉まる音）
は？お　おい！
Hey!
ベル坊　どうした？お～い　ベル坊。
グ～。
Baby Beel, what's wrong?
Hey, Baby Beel!
何してんだ　お前。おい古市
気絶してないで手伝え！
What're you doing?
Hey, Furuichi! Stop being
unconscious and help me!
ベル坊が閉じこもった。
は？何　お前　何かしたのか？
Baby Beel's shut himself in a locker!
Huh? What?
What'd you do?
なんもしてねえよ。おい　ベル坊
開けろ！
I didn't do anything!
Hey, Baby Beel, open up!
ペ！
おい！
Hey!
（寧々）≪は～疲れましたね…≫
何？
What the hell...
し～。も　戻って来た。
T-They've come back!
（寧々）
≪まったく　アイツらといると
気が休まりませんよ≫
Man, I just can't let my
guard down with them around.
バカ　何で隠れた？事情を→
You idiot! Why are we hiding?
Shouldn't we explain what's going on?
説明すりゃあ良かっただろうが。
（由加）≪ホント　ガキっすよね≫
Seriously...
（邦枝）≪早く終わらせましょう≫
Let's get this over with.
Yeah...
最悪だ。何だ　この状況。
This sucks.
How'd we end up like this?
Hey Baby Beel! It's lunchtime!
お～い　ベル坊　ごはんですよ。
くそ。おい古市　お前も何か…。
Damn it...
Hey, Furuichi.
How about you do something?
《フ…。古市です。
という訳で　オレ達は今→
Furuichi here.
And that's how we got into this situation.
こんな状態になってます》
（邦枝）≪ちょ　ちょっと≫
H-Hey!
Madam Aoi, you have such a
slender body as always...
（由加）
≪姐さん　相変わらず
スレンダーボディーっすね≫
Stop touching me, okay?
（邦枝）≪だから　触らないの≫
（由加）≪え　いいじゃないっすか≫
Why not? Just a little...
Oga...
男鹿。
あ？
What?
I want your opinion.
お前の意見を聞きたい。この場合のスレンダーっていうのは→
In this context, what do you
think slender refers to?
どこが。
マジメにやれや　ボケ！
Take this seriously, you dunce!
You idiot! We'll be found out!
（古市）≪ば　バカ…。男鹿
ばれる　ばれる≫
ん？何か言った？
え？
スレンダーボディーっすねって。
Did you say something?
Uh, about your slender body...
No, not that...
いや　そうじゃなくって…。
っていうか離しなさい！
And stop touching me!
わ　分かった分かった。とにかく
向こうに　ばれないように→
Okay, okay!
Anyway, we have to continue to coax
him out without them noticing!
説得　続けろ。それしか　ねえだろ。
ちっ…おい　ベル坊　出て来い。
That's the only choice we have!
Hey, Baby Beel! Come out!
I'll give you a piggyback ride or whatever!
おんぶでも何でもしてやっから！
Piggyback
ダァー？
((ダーブー))
イー。
Oh, Chiaki... Did you grow a little bigger?
（寧々）あれ？千秋　あんた
少し大きくなった？
（千秋）本当ですか？
ハッ！
Really?
And wait, didn't you get bigger, Nene-san?
（由加）ってか　寧々さんも大きく
なってないっすか？
（寧々）え？私は変わんないわよ。
Me? No, I haven't changed.
んぐ～。
小声
おお？そうだ　ベル坊　出て来い！
That's right, Baby Beel! Come on out!
What are you doing, Oga?
小声
（古市）ここで何すんだよ！
And what the hell do you think you are doing?
小声
お前こそ何やってんだよ！
うわ！
ヒョー！
He was so close to coming out!
小声
せっかく出てきそうだったのに！
ふざけんな！てめえ。
Screw you, asshole!
N-No! I didn't do it on purpose!
ち　ちがう！わざとじゃ。
（物音）
ん？
You're up next, Madame Aoi.
次　姐さんっすよ。
Madame Aoi?
（寧々）姐さん？
あ　ああ。ごめん。
Oh, sorry...
小声
ダメだ…出てこねえ。
Crap... He ain't coming out...
小声
ダメだ…なんも見れねえ。
Crap... I can't see squat...
That's not the problem!
お前なあ！
（邦枝）じゃ机を戻しましょうか。
Okay, let's put the desks back.
Where did this desk go?
（由加）この机　どこっすか～？
W-What'll we do?
小声
ちょ…どうすんだ！？
ぐっ…いちか　ばちかだ。
It's sink or swim...
（由加）んん！ん！
ダブ…アイ！？
It was basically like this.
（寧々）大体こんなもんですかね？
Right.
（邦枝）そうね　後は記録を先生の
ところに持って行って。
All that's left is to take
the records to the teacher.
（古市・男鹿）ハー。
（扉の開く音）
H-Hey! Don't come out now!
《ば…！お前！今出てくんな！》
Go back!
《戻れ！》
あ？
アーッ！！
（ヌイグルミ）((イヒヒヒ))
ダー。
ハア…。
（女子達）あ～つかれた。
Phew...
（古市・男鹿）く…っ　ハー。
し　死ぬかと思った。
あ～！クソ！
I-I thought I was dead meat...
God damn it!
後は。
All that's left is...
Hey, Baby Beel!
おら　ベル坊！いつまで
そこにいる気だ！？
How long are you gonna be in there?
いいかげんに出て来い！
プン！
Come on out already!
Come on, Baby Beel!
こら！ベル坊！
にょ！？
((ダブダブ))
((グオー))
((ビー！ダーブ！ダーブ！))
((アハー))
((ダーブー！))
ダブダ！
ん？
Hey, Oga... Isn't this...?
おい男鹿　これって。
あ？
うっ！
What are you two doing?
あんたたち　何してんの？
A-And, why are you in the classroom?!
てゆ～か！な　な　なんで
教室の中にいんの！？
ハッ…あ～！まさか
さっきの物音！
Don't tell me, that sound from before was...
Wait! Hold it...
いや！待て待て。落ち着けって。
Calm down.
You expect me to stay calm?!
落ち着けるかあああ！
（バキ！）
ん？
Looks like they finally went and did it.
あいつら
とうとうやらかしたか。
I can't believe this!
信じらんない！
何してんの！？あんたたち！
What the hell were you doing?!
Where were you peeping from?
どっから覗いてたわけ！？
え！？ち　ち　ちがいます！
N-No, we didn't see anything!
見てないです！スレンダー
ボディーは見てないです！
I didn't see any slender bodies at all!
ハッ！
ふう…フッ。
H-Hey!
お　おい。
心配しなくても
痛みは感じないわよ。
You needn't worry. I'll
make sure it's painless.
ひいあああっ！
何だ！今の音は！ケンカか！？
What was that noise? A fight?
ああっ！せ　先生！助かった～。
S-Sensei! I'm saved...
What? What are you talking about?
なに？どういうことだ。ん？
What the hell is this?!
って　なんだ　これは！？
いえ　何でもありません。
Oh, it's nothing...
机がもろくなっていた
みたいですね～。
The desks seem to have become brittle.
はあ？そんなわけ…。
ハッ！
What? That's not...
（バキッ）
ああ～！
ほら。だから今
掃除しようとしてたんです。
See?
That's why I was about to clean up.
そうよね？古市く～ん。
Isn't that right, Furuichi-kun?
あああ…そうですぅ！
しかし！
Yes!
But...
これクラスの
身体測定の結果です。
These are the results for the class physical.
確認してください。
ぐっ。
Please check them over.
ちっ。
も　もう行っちゃうんですか！？
You're leaving already?
なんだ？何かあるのか？
What? You need me for something?
Nope!
あ…あ…。
いいえ。お疲れ様でした。
Thanks for your hard work...
ったく！
Sheesh.
Now then...
さて…。
だから話を聞けって！
I'm telling you to listen to me!
そもそもベル坊が！
Baby Beel is still...
ハァ！？えっあっどこ行った？
Where'd he go?
ん…ダッ！
何してんだ！あいつ。
What the hell does he think he's doing?
ダダダダ。
ちょっと！逃げる気！？
Hey! You trying to escape?
ちげ～つってんだろ。
あとで説明する。
I told you, you've got it wrong!
I'll explain to you later.
H-Hey! Hold it!
よっ。
ちょちょっと！待ちなさいよ！
なんだっていうの！まったく！
What is the matter with him?
さて…ガッ！
Now then, I'll just...
Oh? Where do you think you're going?
で…？どこ行くの？あんたは。
あ　あの…。
U-Um...
Damn! I just can't catch them out!
クソ！なかなか尻尾を
出しやがらねえ。
≪こら！ベル坊！≫
ん？
Hey, Baby Beel!
ダダダダダ。
Oh, yeah... Why does that bastard
Oga have a kid with him anyway?
《そうだ　そもそも
あの男鹿って奴は→
なんで　あんなガキ　連れてんだ》
ダーイーイー！
ダーブダーブ！
アゥ！
（佐渡原）《しかも素っ裸で→
Look at him! Loitering around buck naked!
ウロウロしやがって》
ダーイーアー！
Hey, he's messing with someone's car!
（佐渡原）《おいおい　誰かの車に
イタズラしてるよ》
《しかもオレが苦労して買った
車に　そっくりだ》
That car looks just like the
car I worked so hard to buy...
Ah... He opened the door and went inside!
《あ～あ～ドア開けて
中入っちゃったよ！》
《そこに男鹿まで来て》
And now here comes Oga, too...
Now he's messing with the car?
《こいつもイタズラかあ？》
Well, sucks to be that guy,
but at least it's not my car.
《ま　こう言っちゃなんだけど
俺の車じゃなくて良かった～》
《屋上にでも行って
気分転換するか》
Maybe I'll head to the roof and cool my head.
（佐渡原）
《ホント　車ってのは
持ってる者にとっては宝石→
Yeah, a man's car is like
his shining jewel...
It's an extension of himself.
いや　自分自身だからな～》
Hey! Come out of there, Baby Beel!
おらあ！出て来い！ベル坊！
ダーブー。
Nothing is worse than
having your car soiled
（佐渡原）
《ピカピカに磨き上げた車を→
by some random person after
you've polished it to a shine.
他人に汚されるのだけは
絶対にイヤだもんな～。→
特にオレの車なんて日本に数台
しかない貴重なヤツだからな。→
And besides, my car is really
valuable! Only a few in all of Japan!
もうコレ地球の宝ですよ。
ホント　マジな話→
It's already a treasure on earth...
I mean, seriously...
あ～。そういや　オフクロ
元気にしてっかな～→
So, I wonder how my mom's doing?
よ～くガキの頃　言われたっけ。→
She was always telling me when I was a kid...
お前はイヤな事から目をそらせる
所があるから注意しろって》
"Watch out, 'cause you have times
you avoid facing harsh realities..."
Open the damn door!
≪ドア外すぞ！コラー！≫
Yeah, my mom wasn't lying, was she?
（佐渡原）
《いや～オフクロの言葉に
ウソはねえな。→
ありがと　オフクロ。
オレ　逃げてたよ。→
Thank you, Mom. I've been running away.
That's my car, isn't it?!
あれ　オレの車じゃね～かよ！》
Hey, Baby Beel! What are you doing?
おい！ベル坊！何してんだ。
ダ！
ダ～！
フゥ　…ン？
What the hell kind of smug look
is that? Get out here now!
なんだ　そのドヤ顔！
とっとと降りてこいや！
アイ？ア　アウー。
ニョ？
キー！キッキッ。
何してんだ！おい！
What're you doing?
Hey!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
お～～い！何してんだ！
いや　なんか
ドアが開かね～んだよ。
Uh, the door won't open.
はあ！？
I-It's broken! What have you done?
こ　壊れてる。お前　何したんだ！
なんもしてね～よ！
I ain't done anything!
Do you have any idea how
expensive this car is?
どれだけ高いか　わかってんのか？
１０年ローンだぞ！
It's a 10-year loan!
知らね～よ。んなこと。
Not my problem.
アブブ…。
Damn it! Well, if you do anything
else to this car, you're...
クソ！とにかく　これ以上
この車に何かしたら…。
（ジョー）
ん？
ぐあ！な　なんだ！？
What the...
う～。
こんなタイミングで
もらしてんじゃね～よ！
Now's not the time to spring a leak!
もらす！？何を何を何を！？
A leak?! What are you...
センセー　赤ん坊が
もらすといえばアレっすよ。
Sensei, when a baby springs
a leak, it's you know...
ホラ　おし…。
やめて～！聞きたくな～い！
You know, pi...
Don't say it! I don't want to know!
Whatever.
しゃあねえな。割るか。桃太郎的に。
I'll have to split it...
Like Momotaro's peach.
えっ何？割る？
お前　割るって言った！？
What? Split it? Did you just say split it?
心配すんな　先生。
きれいに割るんで。
Don't worry, Sensei. I'll
split it nice and clean.
Oh... That's a load off...
そうか…じゃあ安心
…じゃね～よ！
...of crap!
Stop it! I told you I have a 10-year loan!
お　おい！やめろ！
１０年ローンだって言っただろ！
そ　それに教師の車を
これ以上　傷つけてみろ！
And if you do any more harm to a
teacher's car, you're expelled!
退学だぞ～！
退学？
Expelled?
（ジョー）
ふぅぅ～。
先生…心配すんなって。
Sensei...
I told you not to worry.
I'll split it cleanly.
きれいに割るから。
聞いてた！？バカなの！？
Are you listening? Are you an idiot?
バカっす。
だからか…。
I am an idiot!
Oh, that's why...
...hell no!
じゃね～よ！
男鹿！桃太郎式チョーップ！
Oga, Peach Splittin' Chop!
（壊れる音）
ローンが！
My loan!
ウブブブ。ア？ダーブ！
バカだなぁ　こうやって
開けりゃいいだろ。
Silly me! I should have
just opened it this way.
Come here.
来いよ。
ダー！
って　おもらしで
ビショビショじゃね～か！
You're drenched in pee!
That's gross.
きたね～な～。
えへえへえへ。
アハハハ！あ～。
ったく。
Sheesh... Let's go back.
帰るぞ。
アイ！
Uh, first... You didn't open the door!
えっと…まずドア　開けてね～よ！
ってオイ！
Listen, I'm gonna make
this a problem for you!
問題にするからな。
間違いなく退学だぞ！
You're gonna be expelled for sure!
Do you understand this, Oga?
わかったのか！男鹿～！
Principal's Office
What do you mean it's not a problem?
（佐渡原）問題にならないって
どういうことですか！？
After all, Sadohara-sensei, one punch
could never demolish an entire car.
（校長）
だって佐渡原先生。いくらなんでもパンチ１発で車が粉々って。
それはありえないでしょう。
普通の高校生なんでしょ？
Nobody would believe that.
He's a normal high-school student yes?
ええ！まあ…いや…。
Well, yeah... But it's the truth!
でも本当なんです！
本当にあいつが！
He actually...!
You said it was a very high-priced car...
高級な車だったんですってね～。→
I can understand your frustration, at least.
まあ　つらい気持ちは
わかるけどねえ。
That's not the problem!
（佐渡原）
そうじゃないんですよ！あ～！！
Special Class
（邦枝）そうだったの！？
That's what it was?
You should have just explained
the situation to me.
そういうことなら
説明すれば良かったじゃない。
Wasn't it you who attacked me
before I had a chance to explain?
説明する前に殴りかかって
きたのは　お前だろうが。
あっ…。
（古市）ごめんなさい。
ごめんなさい。
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
ごめんなさい。ごめんなさい。
アーウッチ。
Don't go too crazy now, Baby Beel.
はしゃいでんじゃねえぞ。ベル坊。
ダ？
It's all because you locked
yourself up like that.
元はといえば
お前が閉じこもったりするから→
こんなことになったんだろうが。
ア！
That's why it happened.
ところで　ほ　ほんとに
見てないんでしょうね？
By the way... You didn't
actually see anything, right?
見てね～っつってんだろ。
ハー　まったく。
I didn't see a thing.
Sheesh...
Here.
はい　これ。
あ？
You dropped this yesterday... Is it his?
あんた　昨日　落としたでしょ？
その子の？
ダ！アイー。
Never seen the thing...
知らね～ぞ　こんなもん。
ん？
Baby Beel?
ベル坊！？
マッ！
ベル坊～！
Baby Beel!
What's wrong, Baby Beel?
He's crying to let him join
in the preview this time.
Okay, got it! You try doing
the preview this time!
Crap, this isn't previewing anything.
On the next Beelzebub: What
Are the 6 Holy Knights?
So there are strong guys
even at St. Ishiyama?
These 6 Holy Knights sound like fun!